Guide to the Margaret Taylor Smith Papers, 1918-2010 and undated, bulk 1980-2008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2011-0077), 1982-2000, (1 box)
  - Mother, I Have Something to Tell You (Box 35)
    - Correspondence re: Henry A. Murray Research Center, data, publication, 1983-1984
  - Talks, 1993-2000, (2 folders)